他的心跳率飙高了
His heart rate just spiked.
因为那个人不是我
That's because it isn't me.
声音量态完全不稳定
Vocal patterns is all off the hook.
是哪里出了错
This has to be wrong.
大错特错  我没有  我
This is wrong! I didn't...
对  当时有个人  有支机器手
Look, there was a guy with a robot hand.
是他偷走刺客
He stole the Assassin,
他扫描我的脸陷害我
and he scanned my face to frame me.
对  听起来很合理
That sounds plausible,
也不像你临时编造的
and not like something you just made up.
听起来好像是  瞎扯
Sounds a little Scooby-Doo, bro.
不是我
It isn't me!
好的  我说得明白一点
Okay, so, just to be clear...
一名男子  有着机器手  跟蓝斯的脸孔
there's a man with a robot hand and Lance's face
他拿走了M9刺客
who took the  Assassin.
大家都同意吗
We all feel good about that?
好的  完全破了  下班了
Okay, case closed. Let's go home.